{
    "subject": "resource/Republic_of_Texas",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Republic of Texas",
    "human_readable": "The name of Republic of Texas is Republic of Texas.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9754407405853271,
            "question": "What is the official name of the Republic of Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9467315673828125,
            "question": "Is the name of the Republic of Texas different from its official designation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9167227149009705,
            "question": "Could you provide the full name of the Republic of Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9158182740211487,
            "question": "Was there a formal process for establishing the name of the Republic of Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8779538869857788,
            "question": "Are there any other names or designations historically associated with the Republic of Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8653538823127747,
            "question": "How did the name 'Republic of Texas' come to be used?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.819537341594696,
            "question": "How is the name 'Republic of Texas' used in modern contexts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8043041229248047,
            "question": "Does the name 'Republic of Texas' accurately reflect its identity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7353826761245728,
            "question": "What factors might have influenced the choice of name for the Republic of Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6851836442947388,
            "question": "What historical period is associated with the Republic of Texas?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Republic of Texas is Republic of Texas.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9280_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What factors might have influenced the choice of name for the Republic of Texas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9280_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the name 'Republic of Texas' accurately reflect its identity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9280_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is the name 'Republic of Texas' used in modern contexts?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9280_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9280_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9280_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9280_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9280_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9280_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9280_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9280_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9280_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9280_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9280_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it is explicitly stated that:\n\n* The Republic of Texas was a sovereign state (The Republic of Texas states...)\n* It existed from March 2, 1836, to February 19, 1846. (This information is present in multiple documents.)\n* Its name was indeed \"Republic of Texas\" (as shown in the provided context and Wikipedia article on The Republic of Texas)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information clearly states, \"It was called The Republic of Texas. The Wikipedia article on The Republic of Texas states:\" which directly supports the query that the name of the Republic of Texas is indeed \"Republic of Texas.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}